Jacob Fenn<u>er</u>

Web Developer

Contact

Address Springdale, OH, 45246

Phone (605) 261-7237

E-mail jacobgfenner@gmail.com

Portfolio
https://fennerstudios.com

LinkedIn
https://linkedin.com/in/jc
cob-fenner-9496aa197

Hard Skills

React/Redux

Sass

jQuery

Bootstrap

Material-ui

Node/Express

MySQL

Git

TypeScript

Soft Skills

Collaboration

Communication

Dedication

Leadership

Goal-oriented web developer who brings strong commitment to collaboration and solutions-oriented problem-solving. Use various web design packages to develop custom, customer-focused websites and designs. Committed to high standards of user experience, usability, and speed. Specialize in front end development with React.js.

Work History

2021/05 -2021/09

Front End Developer

Booth Or Table LLC, Sioux Falls, SD

- Designed, implemented, and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements.
- Reviewed and tested customer-facing prototypes before deployment, applying best practice diagnostic techniques to verify usability.
- Worked closely with a small team of developers, utilizing version control best practices and paired programming sessions.
- Enhanced code to be more scalable for future expansion by converting to react/redux toolkit.
- Composed clean and efficient code with TypeScript.

2017/03 -Current

Alternate Trombonist

Sioux City Symphony Orchestra, Sioux City, IA

- Prepared necessary concert repertoire with precision and timeliness.
- Supported other musicians with a strong foundation in intonation, core of sound, and rhythmic precision.
- Stepped in for other trombonists on short notice when they had unforeseen commitments and filled in for additional parts as the music required.
- Practiced 35 hours per week to maintain and improve technical skills outside of normal activities and work.

Education

2019/09 -

Master of Arts: Trombone Performance

2021/04

University of Cincinnati - CCM - Cincinnati, OH

2015/08 -2019/05 Bachelor of Arts: Music Education, All Grades Education

Augustana University - Sioux Falls, SD

Recent Project

TIMOTHY ANDERSON, TROMBONE

Professional musician's website -https://www.timothyandersontrombone.com/

- Created website for world renowned trombonist and teacher, Timothy Anderson using React and custom styling with Sass.
- Commerce.js integrated for his online merchandise and stripe for an easy checkout and payment flow.
- Quantity and quality of applications to his studio at the University of Cincinnati,
 College-Conservatory of Music were greater than any other year following deployment of his website.